[{"question": " hey! what are you guys looking at?", "answer": " oh, it&#146;s a poster for that world war i movie that i&#146;m in, check it out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " yeah? wow! it looks really violent!", "answer": " uh-huh! i know. i&#146;m coming soon to a theater near you! i&#146;m in thx! i&#146;m unsuitable for children!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " now i cannot wait to see this.", "answer": " yeah, yeah, it&#146;s already generating oscar buzz.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " i started that!", "answer": " i thought i did! oh hey guess what? the premiere is next week and you&#146;re all invited!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " are we gonna take a limo?", "answer": " sure! why not?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " oh i love taking limos when nobody died!", "answer": " well obviously i won&#146;t be able to come, for those of you who haven&#146;t checked their calendars today is my due date. well y&#146;know, i just want to take a moment and thank you guys for how great you&#146;ve been during this time. i really couldn&#146;t have done it without you. and i have loved these last nine months! and even though i am so looking forward to the next part, i am really gonna miss being pregnant.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " that&#146;s right, still no baby!  come on people! please make some room!", "answer": " uh sweetie, maybe you&#146;d be more comfortable here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " you. like you haven&#146;t done enough.", "answer": " look, i-i know how miserable you are, i wish there was something i can do. i mean i wish i were a seahorse.  because with seahorses it&#146;s the male, they carry the babies. and then also umm, i&#146;d be far away in the sea.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " god.  i have never been so uncomfortable in my entire life!", "answer": " oh i know, i&#146;ve been there. i remember toward the end&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": "  oh phoebe, that&#146;s a great story. can you tell it to me when you&#146;re getting me some iced tea?   oh god, get out! get out!! get out!! get out!!", "answer": " let&#146;s.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " hey! did you have the baby yet?", "answer": " do you want me to come over there and sit on you? &#145;cause i&#146;ll do it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " what are you doing here so early?", "answer": " they sent me home from work. they were like, &quot;start your maternity leave now! just rest, get ready for the baby.&quot; well y&#146;know what? screw &#145;em! if they don&#146;t want me there, i&#146;ll just hang out with you guys.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " hello?", "answer": " joey! it&#146;s estelle! great news, i was able to get you and one guest tickets to your premiere.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " one guest? you told me i can have six tickets!", "answer": " well, i sold four of them on ebay. you&#146;ll be sitting next to hotguy372.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " oh my god. so that&#146;s it?! i only get to bring one guest?", "answer": " yeah, what time do you wanna pick me up?  hello?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": "  did you hear that? i only get one extra ticket to my premiere. so some how i have to pick between you three and ross.", "answer": "  what-what about me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " you said you didn&#146;t want to go.", "answer": " i don&#146;t. but i would still like to be acknowledged. what? just because i&#146;m pregnant you think i&#146;m invisible.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " definitely not invisible.", "answer": " well, well ross didn&#146;t care enough to be here, so i think he&#146;s out. you snooze you lose.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " he&#146;s not snoozing, he&#146;s teaching a class.", "answer": " well then somebody&#146;s snoozing. joey, not that this uh should affect you at all, but if you were to pick me, i was planning on wearing a sequined dress, cut down to here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " i haven&#146;t seen this dress.", "answer": " star in a movie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " joey, you pick who ever you want. okay? you just listen to your heart. what does it tell you?  phoebe, phoebe.", "answer": " well uh&#133;i think i want to take chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " you really want to take me?", "answer": " yeah! yeah! i mean i&#146;m sorry, i wish i can take everybody, but y&#146;know chandler always supported my career. he&#146;s paid for acting classes and head shots and stuff and well this will be my way of paying you back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " so you&#146;re never actually going to pay me back?", "answer": " wait a minute, just because he paid for your head shots you&#146;re gonna take him? joey, i don&#146;t think you&#146;re comprehending just how slutty this dress is!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " it&#146;s not just the stuff he paid for, i mean it&#146;s-it&#146;s everything. y&#146;know? he read lines with me. he-he went with me on auditions when i was really nervous, and then he consoled me after i didn&#146;t get parts that i really wanted. you always believed in me man. even, even when i didn&#146;t believe in myself.", "answer": " i always knew you were gonna make it. i&#146;m so proud of you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " mon, maybe one of these guys wants to wear your dress.", "answer": "  i&#146;m gonna go shave.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " when she comes out, you hold her nose, i&#146;ll blow in her mouth, and the kid will just  right out of her.", "answer": " she&#146;s over a week late! she gotta have it today, right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " i don&#146;t know. i-i think it&#146;s still gonna be a while.", "answer": " hmm, care to make it interesting? i&#146;ll bet you that she&#146;ll have it by this time tomorrow.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " you&#146;re on!", "answer": " okay, how much?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " one hundred thousand dollars!", "answer": " how about fifty bucks?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " fine! i&#146;ll call zurich and move some money around.", "answer": "  all right, who&#146;s turn is it to help me get up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " this is so exciting! it&#146;s so glamorous! people taking our picture. how do i look?", "answer": " a little tall.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " do you mind crouching down a little bit, so that i look taller?  there you go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " oh hey mon? rach is here! ohh, you&#146;re still pregnant. oh, i&#146;m sorry. i know how uncomfortable you are. y&#146;know what? you look great. yeah, like fifty bucks.", "answer": " oh, i have to go pee. apparently this baby thinks that my bladder is a squeeze toy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " it&#146;s interesting that you lost. now, i forget, do you like to lose?", "answer": " now stop it! double or nothing that she has it by tomorrow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " fine! you&#146;re on!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " until then, general grant, why don&#146;t you set up camp  right there.", "answer": "  hey is rachel here? we have a doctor&#146;s appointment.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " she&#146;s in the bathroom.", "answer": " rach, we gotta go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " in a minute!!!", "answer": " people ask me why we&#146;re not together, i just don&#146;t know what to tell them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": "  all right, all right. let&#146;s go!", "answer": " uh, do you wanna go change first? the doctor&#146;s keeping the office open late for us, but if you hurry&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " no, i&#146;m fine.", "answer": " really? you don&#146;t think that&#146;s a little inappropriate.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " good god man don&#146;t anger it.", "answer": " ross, it is 100 degrees outside. for the first time in weeks, i am somewhat comfortable.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " fine! fine! y&#146;know what? whatever you want. okay? you&#146;re the mommy.", "answer": " oh uh-uh pal! don&#146;t call me mommy! it&#146;s bad enough you call your own mother that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": "  &quot;i thought i knew who the enemy was, but it was you all along.&quot;", "answer": "  okay, this is it. it&#146;s my big fight scene coming up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " ross.", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " can i ask you something?", "answer": " uh-huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " when carol was pregnant with ben&#133;", "answer": " mmm?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " &#133;were you this irritating?", "answer": " wow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " excuse me?!", "answer": " oh nothing. nothing! just uh, you&#146;ve been a little short with me lately. i&#146;m not trying to irritate you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " well then you just must have a natural talent for it.", "answer": " y&#146;know what? the doctor will be in soon, why don&#146;t we not speak until then.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": "  okay.  seriously, breathe louder ross! that&#146;s great!", "answer": " y&#146;know we should probably ask the doctor if she even knows how to deliver a baby that&#146;s half human and half pure evil!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " hi dr. long, how are you?", "answer": "  oh, you&#146;re nice to her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " she has the drugs!", "answer": " we&#146;ll do a quick check.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " so, eight days late huh?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " you must be a little uncomfortable.", "answer": " eh, just a tad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " you&#146;re about 80 percent effaced, so you&#146;re on your way. it still could last a little while longer. if you&#146;re anxious there are a few ways to help things along.", "answer": " do them!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " actually, they&#146;re things you can do. just some home remedies, but in my experience i&#146;ve found that some of them are quite effective.", "answer": " well, we are ready to try anything.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " okay, there&#146;s an herbal tea you can drink.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " you can take some caster oil, there&#146;s eating spicy foods&#133;", "answer": " great! we will do all of those.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " good job joe! well done! top notch!", "answer": " you liked it? you really liked it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " oh-ho-ho, yeah!", "answer": " which part exactly?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " the whole thing! can we go?", "answer": " oh no-no-no, give me some specifics.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " i love the specifics, the specifics were the best part!", "answer": " hey, what about the scene with the kangaroo? did-did you like that part?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " i was surprised to see a kangaroo in a world war i epic.", "answer": " you fell asleep!! there was no kangaroo! they didn&#146;t take any of my suggestions! that&#146;s for coming buddy. i&#146;ll see you later.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " what did the doctor say? any news on when the baby will come?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " no. but she did give us some ideas on how to induce labor.", "answer": " yeah, we tried them all. we went for a walk, uh we tried a special tea, caster oil, spicy food nothing has worked.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " well, there is one thing that we haven&#146;t tried, but someone thinks that,  &quot;that will open up a can of worms.&quot;", "answer": " well what is it? what is it? if it&#146;s gonna help bring the baby here, like today. i mean, i think you should do it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " it&#146;s sex.", "answer": " do it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " monica!", "answer": " i&#146;m just saying it&#146;s been a really long time for you. i mean, women have needs. do it, get yours!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " oh i-i don&#146;t know about that. no, i think that if the two of you had sex the-the-the repercussions would be catastrophic.", "answer": " all right, let&#146;s be practical, if ross isn&#146;t willing to do it, he&#146;s not the only guy in the world you can have sex with. you can borrow chandler&#151;chandler is good!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " monica, what is the matter with you?", "answer": " nothing. i just want the baby to be born today.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " why? why today?", "answer": " okay fine! i keep betting phoebe that you&#146;re gonna have the baby and i don&#146;t want to lose again!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " i&#146;ll take that bet.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " well, i&#146;m miserable here! i might as well make some money out it!", "answer": " can i get some of that action?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " wait a minute! now i&#146;m betting against all three of you?", "answer": " oh honey, don&#146;t worry. i really do feel like tomorrow&#146;s the day.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " hey! sleeping beauty!", "answer": " where have you been?! i tried to call you! i want to talk to you! i still feel so bad!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": "  oh no, were you upset? did you lose sleep?", "answer": " i&#146;m so sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " uh-huh look, the only reason i can over here was to settle things between us! okay? you&#146;ve done a lot for me and my career, i wanted to pay you back so i took you to the premiere but you missed it! okay, so how much do i owe you?", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " give me a number, i don&#146;t want to owe you anything!", "answer": " you don&#146;t owe me anything, i don&#146;t want you money&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " ah-ah-ah! we&#146;re doing this! okay, now you got me my first set of head shots. right, how much were those?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know, five hundred dollars?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " okay, five hundred dollars. what else?", "answer": " well then there was the second set, the infamous booger head shots.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " do you want a calculator?", "answer": " please!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " all right, what else?", "answer": " well uh, there was acting classes, stage combat classes, tap classes&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " which we&#146;re still keeping under our hats!", "answer": " uh then there was that dialect coach who helped you with that play where you needed a southern accent. which after twenty hours of lessons still came out jamaican.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " what the hell are you talking about,  &quot;the south will rise again man.&quot;", "answer": " yes, money well spent!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " yeah. okay, what else? rent!", "answer": " okay, two, three years of rent, utilities, food&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " come on, finish your enchilada.", "answer": " ross i&#151;we tried all the spicy food. it&#146;s not working.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " okay here, have one of these peppers. oh ha&#133; oh god! so&#133;so hot!  oh my&#151; by the way, you don&#146;t want to touch the pepper and then touch your eye.", "answer": " i am feeling nothing. speaking of hot, watching you do that really makes me want to have sex with you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " stop it.", "answer": " oh come on ross, why are we wasting our time with this other stuff?! we know what&#146;s gonna work! it&#146;s doctor recommended!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " i&#146;m sorry, but we have to have some boundaries! my god, i&#146;m dying.", "answer": " oh come on ross, we&#146;ve done it before we&#146;ll do it again, it&#146;ll be a nice way to bookend the pregnancy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " this is insane, i&#146;m not gonna make love to you just so that you&#146;ll go into labor.", "answer": " make love? what are you a girl?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " always a great way to get in a man&#146;s pants.", "answer": " but you will, you will be performing a service. okay? just-just think of me as a ketchup bottle, y&#146;know you sometimes you have to bang on the end of it just to get something to come out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " i love when you talk dirty to me.", "answer": " oh, i know it. you&#146;re right. that&#146;s not sexy. oh&#133;oh!  whoops! oh, i seem to have dropped my fork. let me just bed over and get it.  oh god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " okay enough! this is, this is not going to happen.", "answer": " come on ross! i&#146;m miserable here! come on! you started this, now you finish it! come on wuss, make love to me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " y&#146;know what?", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " forget it.", "answer": " oh wow! what now ross you&#146;re not gonna talk? how on earth will you ever annoy me? oh wait a minute, i know.  i mean you&#146;d think the damn jalepeno would&#146;ve cleared up your sinuses, but no!! that&#146;s not enough&#133;  what are you doing?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": "  oh god!", "answer": " oh, i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " oh no. no-no! i think my water just broke.", "answer": " i am good. okay! okay! uh, i got the pillow! i got the bag! you got the keys?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " okay! i got the keys! okay! okay!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " we&#146;re having a baby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " i didn&#146;t uh, really have time to read this part of the books, but do you think we have time to&#133;", "answer": " not so much.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " two hundred.", "answer": " thank you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " that&#146;s it. i&#146;m done. i don&#146;t care when the baby comes, no more betting.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " hello?  uh-huh.  uh-huh.  okay.  i guess we can bet one more time.", "answer": " is rachel having the baby?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " how did you know that?!  joey! chandler!! it&#146;s time!", "answer": " they&#146;re at the coffeehouse.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " you know everything!! oh wait, double or nothing. i bet you the baby is over seven pounds.  i bet you it has hair.  i bet you it&#146;s a girl.", "answer": " we know it&#146;s a girl!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}]